The flowers in hand waiting for me Every word and poetry won't call me by name
Only baby, the more that you give The less that I need, everyone says I look happy
When it feels right
I know that you're wrong for me Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees Cause they say I'm misery, love's gone funny
It's not your fault I ruined everything And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down there with me
I'm everything they said I would be
La la la, I'm everything they said I would be
I'll put you down slow, love you goodbye Before you let go, just one more time
Took off your clothes, pretend that it's fine A little more hurt won't kill you tonight
My word says you don't look happy Close your eyes
I know that you're wrong for me Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees Cause they say I'm misery, love's gone funny
It's not your fault I ruined everything And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down there with me
I'm everything they said I would be
La la la, I'm everything they said I would be
I know that you're wrong for me Gonna wish we never met on the day I leave
I brought you down to your knees Cause they say I'm misery, love's gone funny
It's not your fault I ruined everything And it's not your fault I can't be what you need
Baby, angels like you can't fly down there with me
Oh, angels like you can't fly down there with me