Hey, you know, you have to let me go.
I know this isn't what you want to hear, but I know you can feel that it's the right thing to do.
Not for me, but for you. I can't give you what you need, what you want, or what you deserve, so
you just have to let me go. You can't keep expecting me to change. You can't keep twisting up the
words I say to fit your expectations of what could be, who will never be what you want us to be.
And for that, I really am sorry. You have no idea how much it hurts me that I hurt you,
because I just can't make myself love you, not in the way that you want, and you shouldn't want that.
Your perfect person will love you just as much as you love them, and you'll never have to question it.
You'll finally understand why I'm not the one for you, why I'm so wrong for you,
but you won't see that until you move past me. Please, move past me. Move on with your life without me.
You have to let me go, and I hope you know, I know that you'll finally meet the person whom you never want to see.
So what you fucking assume? Too cold when you live? Too hot when you live?
If it rained too fucking much, now I'm kind of some real fucking talk.
Maybe you're the only black person applying for a fucking job. Maybe you're the only female.
Maybe you're the only fucking gay person. Job, whatever the fuck it may be. Maybe that's
you in your fucking head. Maybe that's your excuse for not being better. Life's a real big fucking picture.
When I was young, all those things got my head black, fucking not smart enough, single mom,
all that bullshit, old space in my head. If you're allowing people and things and situations
to a space in your fucking head, you're losing. Last thing, last one big fucking head game,
you play with yourself. If you lose, it's because you allow life to get in your fucking head. Stay hard.